<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>USB on 3D Visualization System for Ophthalmic Surgery</title>
    <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/tags/usb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in USB on 3D Visualization System for Ophthalmic Surgery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:23:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/tags/usb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a Doctor Profile</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/doctor_management/add_doctor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:23:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/doctor_management/add_doctor/</guid>
      <description>To create a new doctor profile, perform the following:
 In the Home panel, select the doctor Add button. The New Doctor dialog box opens. In the Name field, enter a profile name. To copy settings from another profile, perform the following:  Click the Copy Settings From toggle switch. Click Local to copy a profile stored on the system or click USB to copy a profile from a connected USB drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camera</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:45:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/camera/</guid>
      <description>The camera is a stereoscopic 3D camera with high dynamic range. Mount the camera on a surgical microscope.
1 Camera &amp;ndash; Captures video from the connected microscope.2 Strain relief screw &amp;ndash; Holds the camera cable in place to reduce stress on the cable connection.3 USB camera connector &amp;ndash; Connects the camera to the cart.4 Iris slider &amp;ndash; Adjusts light exposure captured by the camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accessories</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/accessories/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:46:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/accessories/</guid>
      <description>The system may include the following accessories:
 Lens cap - Protects the camera lens. Cable straps - Secure the camera cable to the microscope. Cable hooks - Route loose cables or coil cable for storage or transportation. Display remote and batteries - Sets the display settings. Use only if directed by Technical Services. The remote may require AA or AAA batteries depending on the display modal. Screen protector - Protects the display when the system is in storage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>