<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>supplemental on 3D Visualization System for Ophthalmic Surgery</title>
    <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/categories/supplemental/</link>
    <description>Recent content in supplemental on 3D Visualization System for Ophthalmic Surgery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 00:03:28 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/categories/supplemental/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide Overview</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/guide_overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:33:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/guide_overview/</guid>
      <description>This user guide contains set up, operation, and other information about the 3D Visualization System.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/guide_overview/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:34:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/guide_overview/terms/</guid>
      <description>The following terms are used in this guide or in the application:
 System - The 3D visualization system, including the cart, display, and camera. Vit System - The Company Vitrectomy Vision system Phaco System - The Company Phacoemulsification Vision System Analysis System - The Company Measurement System  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symbols</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/guide_overview/symbols/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:34:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/guide_overview/symbols/</guid>
      <description>The following symbols and icons are used on the system and in labels:
  Date of Manufacture     Manufacturer     Risk of Electric Shock     Safety Warning   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Warnings and Precautions</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/safety_information/general_warnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:38:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/safety_information/general_warnings/</guid>
      <description>A warning statement is written to protect individuals from bodily harm. A caution statement is written to protect the instrument from damage. This section is for general system warnings and precautions only.
WARNINGUse of accessories other than those provided may affect system performance and create potential hazards. If it is determined that an accessory not provided by the Company has contributed to the malfunction of the equipment during the warranty period, service will be provided at prevailing hourly rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Label Locations</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/safety_information/label_locations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:43:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/safety_information/label_locations/</guid>
      <description>Note the safety and system label locations. Refer to the system for specific information.
1 Moving parts warning label &amp;ndash; Includes a warning related to a protective guard.2 Identifies compatible connectors. &amp;ndash; The location and connector type varies with the display model.3 Oculars storage warning label &amp;ndash; Includes information about storing the microscope oculars.4 Product label &amp;ndash; Includes information about the system.5 Wireless label &amp;ndash; Indicates wireless capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serious incident Reporting</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/safety_information/serious_incident_reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:44:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/safety_information/serious_incident_reporting/</guid>
      <description>Report any serious incident related to the system to the Company. In the EU, also report serious incidents to the competent authority for medical devices for the member state.
Website: www.____.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/settings/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:48:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/settings/about/</guid>
      <description>The About system settings displays general system information, including software version and a copy of the user guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storage and Transportation</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/maintenance/storage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:24:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/maintenance/storage/</guid>
      <description>To store or transport the system within the facility, perform the following:
 Route the camera cable.
a. Disconnect the camera cable from the camera.
b. Wrap camera cable around the camera cable coil. Route the power cable.
a. Disconnect the power cable from the outlet.
b. Wrap power cable around the power cable coil. If the system includes a connected DataFusion device, disconnect the cable on the other device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireless Keyboard Recharging</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/maintenance/basic/keyboard_recharge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:29:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/maintenance/basic/keyboard_recharge/</guid>
      <description>To charge the wireless keyboard, use the micro USB cable to connect the keyboard to a USB connector on the cart. The battery indicator blinks green while charging. Charge it until the indicator light stops blinking. The keyboard can be used while charging. If the battery power is low, the indicator blinks red and the keyboard back light turns off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/maintenance/troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:30:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/maintenance/troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>If the system exhibits the following symptoms, attempt the corresponding troubleshooting procedures before contacting Technical Services.
The image is blurry or out of focus  Use the microscope controls to focus the image on-screen. Check to see that the camera is flush on the microscope. Wearing the 3D glasses, close one eye at a time to check the right and left eye focus for the camera. If the image still appears out of focus or blurry, check the microscope alignment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>External USB Drives</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/additional_information/external_drives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 00:02:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/additional_information/external_drives/</guid>
      <description>To transfer recorded video or snapshots to an external hard drive, connect an the drive to a USB 3.0 connector (recommended) on the cart side panel or a USB 2.0 connector on the cart front panel. The drive must be in exFAT format.
NOTE: Do not use an external hard drive during surgery.
To eject the drive, click Eject Drive on the Home screen or disconnect the drive after a system shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/additional_information/keyboard_shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 00:03:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/additional_information/keyboard_shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>   Key Description     S Take a snapshot   R Start or stop a recording   Ctrl+FN+F1 Swap viewport layout   Ctrl+FN+F2 Swap video source   Ctrl+FN+F3 Switch camera orientation   Ctrl+FN+F4 Cycle imaging modes   Ctrl+FN+F5 Cycle light profiles   Ctrl+FN+F6 Cycle color channels   Ctrl+Insert Increase gain (digitally brighten)   Ctrl+Delete Decrease gain (digitally darken)   W+W White balance   Ctrl+Enter Start case (from the Home screen)   Ctrl+FN+End Shutdown (from the Home screen) or save media and then shutdown (from the Case screen)    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disposal</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/additional_information/disposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 00:03:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/additional_information/disposal/</guid>
      <description>This product complies with the WEEE Directive (2002/96/EC) marking requirement. Do not discard this electronic product in domestic household waste. This is an explanation of how to dispose of this product based on Waste Electrical and Electronic Equipment (WEEE), Directive 2002/96/EC. This directive is only valid in the EU. With reference to the equipment types in the WEEE directive Annex 1, this product is classified as a “Medical Device” product. Do not dispose in domestic household waste.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>