<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hardware on 3D Visualization System for Ophthalmic Surgery</title>
    <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/categories/hardware/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hardware on 3D Visualization System for Ophthalmic Surgery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:12:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/categories/hardware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Label Locations</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/safety_information/label_locations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:43:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/safety_information/label_locations/</guid>
      <description>Note the safety and system label locations. Refer to the system for specific information.
1 Moving parts warning label &amp;ndash; Includes a warning related to a protective guard.2 Identifies compatible connectors. &amp;ndash; The location and connector type varies with the display model.3 Oculars storage warning label &amp;ndash; Includes information about storing the microscope oculars.4 Product label &amp;ndash; Includes information about the system.5 Wireless label &amp;ndash; Indicates wireless capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>System Components</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:45:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/</guid>
      <description>At a minimum, the system includes the cart, camera, microscope, 3D glasses, keyboard, and touchpad. However, the following is an example of a typical setup, including additional devices:
1 System &amp;ndash; Receives video from the camera and displays 3D images.2 Patient Bed &amp;ndash; Holds the patient at a comfortable level.3 Microscope stand &amp;ndash; Suspends a microscope above the patient.4 Camera &amp;ndash; Captures 3D video.5 Microscope &amp;ndash; Magnifies the view of the camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camera Installation</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_setup/system_assembly/camera_installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 21:06:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_setup/system_assembly/camera_installation/</guid>
      <description>Mount the camera to a surgical microscope. Depending on the microscope model, install an L-ring bracket to the camera lens. Ensure the entire optical path is clean and free of dust before attaching the camera.
 Mount ring bracket. Connect the camera to the microscope with the slider facing the user. Loosely wrap the camera cable around the microscope arm so that the cable does not interfere with the surgery or restrict movement of the microscope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secondary Display (Optional)</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_setup/system_assembly/secondary_display/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:09:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_setup/system_assembly/secondary_display/</guid>
      <description>To connect a secondary display, connect the it to the HDMI output connector on the system front panel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Procedure</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_setup/startup_procedure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:15:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_setup/startup_procedure/</guid>
      <description>WARNINGTo avoid risk of electric shock, this equipment must only be connected to a supply mains with protective earth (ground).CAUTIONGrounding reliability can only be achieved when equipment is connected to an equivalent receptacle marked ‘Hospital Grade’.To power the system, perform the following:
 Connect the power cable to a hospital-grade power outlet. Turn on the main power switch. Wait 30 seconds for the system to initialize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>System Placement</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_setup/system_placement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:12:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_setup/system_placement/</guid>
      <description>CAUTIONDo not push or pull unit by the display or any cable. The unit should be pulled and not pushed, especially over elevator and door thresholds.For the best 3D effect, place the display next to the patient bed, between 4′ to 6′ (1.2m to 1.8 m) away from the user. Ensure the screen is at the same height as the user when he or she is seated at the operating table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Display Position</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_setup/display_position/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:12:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_setup/display_position/</guid>
      <description>To place the display at the appropriate level and angle, move the display as follows:
 To adjust the height of the display, carefully lift the display up or down. Avoid putting stress on the top of the display. To rotate the display, push the left or right side of the display. To tilt the display, push or pull the bottom of the display.  Note: If necessary, loosen the adjustment knobs on the display mounting bracket to adjust the tilt and tighten them to secure it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camera</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:45:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/camera/</guid>
      <description>The camera is a stereoscopic 3D camera with high dynamic range. Mount the camera on a surgical microscope.
1 Camera &amp;ndash; Captures video from the connected microscope.2 Strain relief screw &amp;ndash; Holds the camera cable in place to reduce stress on the cable connection.3 USB camera connector &amp;ndash; Connects the camera to the cart.4 Iris slider &amp;ndash; Adjusts light exposure captured by the camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cart</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/cart/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:45:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/cart/</guid>
      <description>The cart receives video input from the camera and additional data from other connected devices, and then outputs the results on the monitor.
1 Primary Display &amp;ndash; Produces 3840 x 2160p 3D resolution video. 3D images require passive, circularly-polarized 3D glasses.2 Cable access &amp;ndash; Routes cables from inside the system to external devices.3 Front panel connectors &amp;ndash; Includes 2 USB, an HDMI output, and a composite connector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Displays</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/displays/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:45:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/displays/</guid>
      <description>Depending on the display model, the system connects to the display either through DisplayPort input 1 or both the HDMI input 3 and COMM cable connector. The system also supports a secondary display to either duplicate the primary display view or show a subset of features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glasses</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/glasses/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:45:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/glasses/</guid>
      <description>3D images require passive, circularly-polarized 3D glasses. If necessary, wear the 3D glasses over prescription glasses.
CAUTIONThe 3D glasses must be worn in front of the laser protective eyewear to avoid distorting the 3D effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard and Mouse</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/keyboard_and_mouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:45:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/keyboard_and_mouse/</guid>
      <description>The system includes both a wired and a wireless keyboard with an integrated touchpad. The wireless keyboard is rechargeable and the battery indicator displays the charge level while the keyboard is on.
1 Power indicator &amp;ndash; Lights according to the battery status Blinking green - The battery is charging. Solid green – The battery has adequate charge. Blinking red – The battery power is low. Recharge the battery.  2 USB connector &amp;ndash; Connects the keyboard to a power source to recharge the batteries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Footswitch (Optional)</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/footswitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:46:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/footswitch/</guid>
      <description>The footswitch performs basic functions during operation through controls operated by a foot.
1 Left push button &amp;ndash; Changes the camera orientation between standard and inverted.2 Right push button &amp;ndash; Starts or stops movie recordings.3 Left pedal &amp;ndash; Cycles to the previous imaging mode.4 Right pedal &amp;ndash; Cycles to the next imaging mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accessories</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/accessories/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:46:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/accessories/</guid>
      <description>The system may include the following accessories:
 Lens cap - Protects the camera lens. Cable straps - Secure the camera cable to the microscope. Cable hooks - Route loose cables or coil cable for storage or transportation. Display remote and batteries - Sets the display settings. Use only if directed by Technical Services. The remote may require AA or AAA batteries depending on the display modal. Screen protector - Protects the display when the system is in storage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>