<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>camera on 3D Visualization System for Ophthalmic Surgery</title>
    <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/tags/camera/</link>
    <description>Recent content in camera on 3D Visualization System for Ophthalmic Surgery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:30:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/tags/camera/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>System Components</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:45:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/</guid>
      <description>At a minimum, the system includes the cart, camera, microscope, 3D glasses, keyboard, and touchpad. However, the following is an example of a typical setup, including additional devices:
1 System &amp;ndash; Receives video from the camera and displays 3D images.2 Patient Bed &amp;ndash; Holds the patient at a comfortable level.3 Microscope stand &amp;ndash; Suspends a microscope above the patient.4 Camera &amp;ndash; Captures 3D video.5 Microscope &amp;ndash; Magnifies the view of the camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/maintenance/cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:24:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/maintenance/cleaning/</guid>
      <description>Clean the system by periodically wiping down with a dry, lint-free cloth. Use warm water and mild detergent on non-electrical system components (for example, the cart, exterior cart panels, and 3D glasses). Wipe down the camera and camera cable with isopropyl alcohol. Wipe the display with a soft, dry cloth. Use less than 0.10 lb. of force on the display. Water-based cleaners may damage the coating on the screen.  CAUTIONDo not immerse or expose electrical components to excessive moisture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storage and Transportation</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/maintenance/storage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:24:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/maintenance/storage/</guid>
      <description>To store or transport the system within the facility, perform the following:
 Route the camera cable.
a. Disconnect the camera cable from the camera.
b. Wrap camera cable around the camera cable coil. Route the power cable.
a. Disconnect the power cable from the outlet.
b. Wrap power cable around the power cable coil. If the system includes a connected DataFusion device, disconnect the cable on the other device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/maintenance/troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 23:30:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/maintenance/troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>If the system exhibits the following symptoms, attempt the corresponding troubleshooting procedures before contacting Technical Services.
The image is blurry or out of focus  Use the microscope controls to focus the image on-screen. Check to see that the camera is flush on the microscope. Wearing the 3D glasses, close one eye at a time to check the right and left eye focus for the camera. If the image still appears out of focus or blurry, check the microscope alignment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Footswitch (Optional)</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/footswitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 22:46:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/system_information/system_components/footswitch/</guid>
      <description>The footswitch performs basic functions during operation through controls operated by a foot.
1 Left push button &amp;ndash; Changes the camera orientation between standard and inverted.2 Right push button &amp;ndash; Starts or stops movie recordings.3 Left pedal &amp;ndash; Cycles to the previous imaging mode.4 Right pedal &amp;ndash; Cycles to the next imaging mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitor</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/settings/system_settings/monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:47:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/settings/system_settings/monitor/</guid>
      <description>The monitor system settings have adjustable settings for displays connected to the system. To access Monitor options, click Monitor.
1 Monitor drop-down menu &amp;ndash; Selects a display.2 Primary Monitor toggle switch &amp;ndash; Sets the selected display to the primary display. Only use the provided monitor as the primary monitor.3 View drop-down menu &amp;ndash; Sets the content on the screen. Select one of the following: Control - Displays the user interface and system camera image.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>