<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Live Case on 3D Visualization System for Ophthalmic Surgery</title>
    <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/live_case/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Live Case on 3D Visualization System for Ophthalmic Surgery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:24:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/live_case/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Layout</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/live_case/procedure_layout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:25:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/live_case/procedure_layout/</guid>
      <description>1 Case timer &amp;ndash; Displays the duration of the surgical case.2 Record video button &amp;ndash; Starts and stops recording video of the screen. A red dot appears next to the case when a case is being recorded.3 Snapshot button &amp;ndash; Takes a picture of the screen.4 Information panel &amp;ndash; Displays basic information to identify the current patient and case.5 Quick Access Bar &amp;ndash; Includes buttons to quickly change various display settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recordings</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/live_case/recordings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:43:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/live_case/recordings/</guid>
      <description>Recordings save video from the camera. To save overlay information, enable the applicable DataFusion feature. Overlay information includes patient and case information from the system, or other data from connected systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Access Bar</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/live_case/quick_access_bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:43:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/live_case/quick_access_bar/</guid>
      <description>The Quick Access Bar contains specified buttons for display options. Click the buttons to quickly change settings or, if available, click the drop-down menu below buttons to select a specific option.
NOTE: To change the available buttons or the options available for a button, see Settings.
Use the Quick Access Bar to change the following display modes and settings:
1 Swap layout &amp;ndash; Changes the number of video inputs displayed on the Case screen (1 or 2).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End Case</title>
      <link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/live_case/end_case/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 23:43:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-example/operation/live_case/end_case/</guid>
      <description>When the case is complete, click End Case. Recordings stop and the following prompts appear:
 If any imaging mode changes were made during the case, select Yes to save the changes or No to delete the changes. If desired, save recorded video. To save a copy of the video to an external hard drive, connect one to a side panel USB connector. If a patient profile was not selected, enter patient information.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>